(Sheldon:)I didn't get to spend a lot of time
with you on this visit.
And whose fauIt was that?
(Leonard:)Yours.
Shelly, you're not 8 years old anymore.
We have to have a different relationship.
(Sheldon:)No, we don't.
(Sheldon:)- The one we have works great.
- Sweetheart, you are a grown man.
(Sheldon:)Or maybe I'm part of a new species
that lives for years...
(Sheldon:)...which means
I'm still basically a toddler.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, I so should have taken you
to Houston.
(Sheldon:)Does this mean
you're not going to sing "Soft Kitty"?
(Mrs Cooper:)No, I will always sing you
"Soft Kitty."
(Mrs Cooper:)Soft kitty, warm kitty, little ball of fur
- Were we supposed to take that pie out?
- Get out!
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, that was rude.
(Sheldon:)Well, I know, but he means well.
(Mrs Cooper:)Sing.
(Mrs Cooper:)Happy kitty, sleepy kitty...
(Sheldon:)What are you trying to pull, Mom?
(Sheldon:)From the top.
(Mrs Cooper(to God):)This is what I'm talking about.
(Mrs Cooper:)Soft kitty, warm kitty, little ball of fur